Phone:+1 209 813 2524

# Joseph Jackson

# **Full Stack Developer**

# **ABOUT ME**

With a year of experience in web developing. I am a full-stack developer specializing in Web. I completed some projects using React, Node, Express and MongoDB. And I also know about Angular, Next, TypeScript and mysql. My deep understanding of based knowledge of Web equips me to excel in any project.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Jan 2023 - NOW

#### **Full Stack Developer**

Upwork

- -Created an information portal for back pain support. Created an online ordering system for emergency medical staff housing mattress and furniture discounts on domestic and foreign items.
- -Created the front end of an invoice management app written in React; it was fully responsive and had a lot of custom inputs and dynamically generated pages.
- -Developed a web application for stock market analyses.

Jun 2021 - Jan 2023

# JavaScript Developer

Freelancei

- -Created a showcase and online order system for a wine company.
- -Created a photo and video contest web app for a US startup. Users could upload photos and videos and participate in contests where the best upload would get prizes. The app was made with scalability in mind.
- -Supported the missions of facilitating workers' compensation claims' data transfers.

May 2020 - May 2021

# Junior Front-end Developer

Self-Employed

- -Worked as a junior front-end developer to improve the app, mainly concerning page optimization.
- -Created a number of responsive web apps and pages.
- -Maintained the existing web dashboard for multi-source power and energy monitoring leveraging React, TypeScript, and Material UI.

# **EDUCATION**

Oct 2015- May 2020

Bachelor Degree of Computer Science - University of California--Berkeley

California

I entered University of California--Berkeley in Oct 2013 and I studied for 4 years and 8 months.

- -Duration: 4 years
- -Curriculum: C++, Python, JavaScript, React, Node, PHP
- -Skills Gained: Problem-solving, analytical thinking, software development, and a solid foundation in computer theory and practical application.

**SKILLS** Node JavaScript

Python PHP

React Angular

Next

LANGUAGES ENGLISH: NATIVE